bannerbank.com 2013-09-01

# FACTS

                                                                                                                               Rev. October 2012
                               WHAT DOES BANNER BANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
 FACTS
 Why?                          Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers
                               the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect,
                               share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we
                               do.
 What?                         The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have
                               with us. This information can include:
                                 l Social Security number                                    l Overdraft history
                                 l Account balances                                          l Account transactions
                                 l Credit history                                            l Checking account information
 How?                          All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business.
                               In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal
                               information; the reasons Banner Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
    Reasons we can share your personal information                           Does Banner Bank share?             Can you limit this sharing?
 For our everyday business purposes -                                                          Yes                          No
 such as to process your transactions, maintain your
 account(s), respond to court orders and legal
 investigations, or report to credit bureaus
 For our marketing purposes -                                                                   No                     We don't share
 to offer our products and services to you
 For joint marketing with other financial companies                                             No                     We don't share
 For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -                                              Yes                          No
 information about your transactions and experiences
 For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -                                              Yes                          Yes
 information about your creditworthiness
 For our affiliates to market to you                                                           Yes                          Yes
 For nonaffiliates to market to you                                                             No                     We don't share
 To limit our                    l Call Toll-free 800-272-9933
 sharing                       Please note:
                               If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this
                               notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in
                               this notice.
                               However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
 Questions?                    Call toll-free 800-272-9933
Privacy Model Disclosure                                                                                                        PRIV-MODEL 8/1/2010
VMP® Bankers Systems™
Wolters Kluwer Financial Services © 2010                               2012.1/1660 3494008-010 Custom EPRV1660

Page 2
What We Do
How does Banner Bank protect   To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use
my personal information?       security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer
                               safeguards and secured files and buildings.
                               We also maintain other physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect
                               this information and we limit access to information to those employees for whom
                               access is appropriate.
How does Banner Bank collect   We collect your personal information, for example, when you
my personal information?         l Open an account                          l Use your credit or debit card
                                 l Pay your bills                           l Make deposits or withdrawals from
                                 l Apply for a loan                            your account
                               We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus,
                               affiliates, or other companies.
Why can't I limit all sharing? Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                 l sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your
                                    creditworthiness
                                 l affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                 l sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                               State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
What happens when I limit      Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
sharing for an account I hold
jointly with someone else?
Definitions
Affiliates                     Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                               non-financial companies.
                                 l Our affiliates include:
                                     l Financial companies such as: Northwest Financial Corporation and
                                        Banner Corporation and its banking affiliates and subsidiaries, Banner
                                        Bank, Islanders Bank, and Community Financial Corporation.
Nonaffiliates                  Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                               non-financial companies.
                                 l Banner Bank does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint Marketing                A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market
                               financial products or services to you.
                                 l Banner Bank doesn't jointly market.
